Ami Kevadiya

Frontend web developer

🔀 amikevadiya05@gmail.com 📞 +61 435332531 💡 Sydney, Australia

Profile

I'm a creative Front End Developer with more than 4.5 years of experience designing and managing responsive websites. HTML, CSS, JQuery, Javascript, Shopify, GravCMS, and WordPress are among my abilities. I have worked with UI/UX tools such as Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma, and XD. In addition, I have over a year of React js experience.

Professional Experience

04/2022 - 01/2023 Surat, India

Sr Frontend Developer

NEXTNOUS

- Created a responsive and adaptive website with HTML5 and CSS3.
- I'm working on few react projects.
- Handle numerous design projects at once and deliver to a high quality.
- Build a website with the Bootstrap framework.
- Added a new feature in websites for better user experience
- · Created and maintained HTML standard for websites.
- Redesigned website with clean, efficient coding that is responsive and userfriendly.
- Created and managed a WordPress website.
- Solid understanding of web design principles.
- Expertise in wireframing, UX/UI design, and prototyping across various devices.
- Design an application logo and banner.
- Designed the user interface for a mobile application in Figma.

04/2021 - 03/2022 Surat, India

Frontend web developer

Dynamic Dreamz

- I worked on a Shopify ecommerce store.
- I'm working on fixing the jQuery problem on Shopify.
- Added a new feature in shopify store for better user experience.
- Create a website using the Bootstrap framework.
- I made an animation using custom jQuery.
- Converted PSD, XD and Figma files to HTML, CSS and jQuery.
- Converted Figma file to Shopify store.
- · Work on numerous projects at the same time, prioritizing activities and ensuring that all projects are completed on schedule.
- Designed responsive and adaptive websites using HTML5 and CSS3.

• To organize work into boards, I used project management software like Jira and Trello.

04/2019 – 03/2021 Surat, India

Frontend web developer

Casepoint Pvt.Ltd.

- We were working on an eDiscovery product.
- I'm familiar with agile scrum and team foundation server (TFS).
- I worked on the Kendo UI library.
- Worked on 508 compliance for eDiscovery product
- I primarily worked on jQuery for 508 compliance.
- I collaborated with the team to include 508 compliance into the product.
- I created a dynamic website with Grav CMS.

05/2018 – 04/2019 Surat, India

Web Designer

Ecreate Infotech

- Designed and developed responsive and adaptive website using HTML5 and CSS3.
- Design, develop, test and deploy design feature in timely manner.
- Build a website with clean and efficient code that is responsive and accessible on all devices, platforms, and is user-friendly.
- Added new feature in website for better user experience.
- Created and maintained HTML standard for website.
- Build a website with the Bootstrap framework.
- Created and managed a WordPress website.
- Worked on ACF field plugin on WordPress.
- Using wow.js, I added animation to the webpage.
- Redesigned website with clean, efficient coding that is responsive and userfriendly.
- Design an application logo and banner.
- Designed the user interface for a mobile application in Photoshop.

Skills

• HTML

CSS

JavaScript

• jquery

Bootstrap

WordPress

• Shopify

Gravcms

Kendo UI

• 508 Compliance

Adobe Photoshop

Illustrator

XD

• Figma

React

Education

06/2018 – 04/2020 Jaipur, India Master of computer application

Suresh Gyan Vihar University

06/2015 – 03/2018 Surat, India

Bachelors in Computer Application

Sutex Bank College of Computer Applications & Science



Portfolio 🗆

Behance 🛮